<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Yuanzi</title>
	<atom:link href="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi</link>
	<description>See the world with different perspectives</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 06:30:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>zh-CN</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Report 2-4</title>
		<link>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/31/report-2-4/</link>
					<comments>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/31/report-2-4/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[W]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 02:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Report]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/?p=190</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Group-6 I was very impressed with Group-6&#8217;s podcast, t&#8230;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Group-6</strong></h2>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">I was very impressed with Group-6&#8217;s podcast, the guests, the content of the dialogue and the post-production were all very professional.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">The topic of this podcast is how to build a personal brand on social media. Firstly, know yourself and find out what makes you unique. For me, this is a very important piece of advice. I had a dream of becoming a freelance artist, but I wasn&#8217;t sure what made me unique as a person. What I&#8217;m good at, what I like and what the public likes, I&#8217;ve been trying to find where these three areas intersect. Maybe I also have to understand and work out in which area I can make my personal identity.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">Also, my guest mentioned updating her social media accounts for a long time, which is something I often forget. I&#8217;m not good at sticking to things, I often try different directions, create different accounts, and abandon and forget my social media accounts because I get busy. If I am determined to run my own social media, I should stick with it as a business.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">Later on, both the guest and the Group6 interview touched on the period of time to start running a personal brand and discussed whether you should start as early as possible or wait until the time is right to start. I&#8217;ve rarely thought about this aspect of my life, and I probably haven&#8217;t been serious enough about running a social media business before. I&#8217;m actually graduating soon and have to start thinking about employment, and personal branding is crucial if I&#8217;m going to be a freelance artist. I have to start thinking deeply and planning how my social media will be run.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Group-5</h2>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">Group-5&#8217;s podcast explores the life of Gen Z influencers.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">I rarely look at Instagram and TikTok and lack knowledge about influencers on both platforms. The life of influencers as depicted in the podcast has greatly expanded my horizons.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">The guest&#8217;s internet persona may be more typical of Singaporean social media platforms, but this type of internet persona is rare on Chinese social media platforms.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">In China, there is not a huge market for very young, asset-hungry, luxury-loving female netizens. Young fashion bloggers usually portray the image of students who use affordable fashion and beauty products. It is only fashion bloggers over twenty-five years old who start discussing luxury goods. In China, the number of young students who can consume luxury goods is small, and few fashion bloggers target this market.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">Society very much discourages young people from high spending, which has to do with the economy, culture and so on. The government does not support young people investing their money in luxuries. East Asian parents are against young people having too much disposable money. Young luxury consumers are not big enough to get a voice in the mainstream media. People who have difficulty consuming luxury goods loathe the image of rich young people. I was struck by the differences in the internet ecosystem presented by this comparison. I started to think that when running social media accounts in different regions, it might be important to have a deep understanding of different social cultures and online ecology. The Internet society is equally society, and perhaps sociological knowledge can help us to have a deeper understanding of the media.<br></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Group-2</h2>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">I really enjoyed this episode of the podcast, meticulously delivered with a lot of useful content. E-commerce is a very promising industry and is closely related to media. In the future, it is foreseeable that the e-commerce sector will demand more and more media professionals. This is a career path to consider.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">The ability to learn will be a basic quality requirement for this industry. The guest mentioned that he and many of his team members did not come from media background, but the guest showed an in-depth understanding of the media field, and you can see that the guest has knowledge of supply chain and other different aspects. E-commerce is a very competitive field in China, and it&#8217;s clear that having media-related knowledge and diploma is not enough.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">The guest shared a lot of personal experience about what it takes to work in the media. I think it can be summarised in one word: ‘Understanding’.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">Understanding of the self, the self is the practitioner himself, or the brand itself. Firstly, media practitioners need to have a clear understanding of their own abilities and passions. Only by knowing what they want to do and what they are capable of doing can they avoid the two great tests of ‘commercialisation’ and ‘high work pressure’ as the guest said. Brands also need to have a clear understanding of themselves, and I think the guest&#8217;s analogy of social media being the face of the brand is a good one. Consumers are no longer paying for illusory brands, and there is a general trend for consumers to be more receptive to brands that ‘feel like a person’. I&#8217;ve seen a lot of brands that are very vague about ‘who I really am’ and ‘what I really look like’, so how can a brand without a face gain the trust of consumers?</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">Understanding of others, the others are collaborators and consumers. Only by understanding the needs of the partners, such as the example of the little girl mentioned by the guest, can we achieve a win-win situation. Only by understanding the competencies of the partner, such as the blogger who is good at presenting scientific knowledge, as mentioned by the guest, can we maximise the effect of the collaboration. The understanding of the consumer is even more important. Firstly, who are you selling to? Second, what do they want? </p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">Media is an industry that serves people, and when you express yourself, you have to be heard, and they can understand and accept it for your expression to be meaningful. This is often not a question of ability but a question of mindset, you need to draw closer to the consumer, deep into their hearts, and even understand and feel what they themselves may not be able to understand and feel.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/31/report-2-4/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report 1</title>
		<link>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/30/report-1/</link>
					<comments>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/30/report-1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[W]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 06:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Report]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/?p=165</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The main takeaway that this assignment gave me was that I ac&#8230;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">The main takeaway that this assignment gave me was that I actually experienced how to communicate and collaborate with professionals or group members.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">After understanding the assignment, I first discussed the list of possible guests to invite with my group. I know a little about freelance painters in China, so I first considered inviting from this field. After contacting several artists, I received some positive responses. In the end, I chose an artist who had experience as a professional cartoonist and was now freelancing and running her own personal media account. Our group thought her career history would be valuable to discuss, so we planned an entire podcast on the topic.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">This guest studied accounting in college, then went on to work in the comics industry before finally choosing to freelance. So I divided the podcast into three parts, the first being how to switch from an unrelated major to drawing comics, the second being the experience of working in comics, and the third being running a personal account. I think these are the areas that will be of interest to the students, and the guest will be able to offer her own experiences.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">I was responsible for planning the podcast, communicating with the guests, hosting the podcast and a little editing. Communicating with the guest put a lot of pressure on me because she had a lot of work experience, was well-known on the Chinese internet, and was much older than me. Negotiating the details of the podcast, scheduling the recording and so on was very stressful. Scheduling takes into account the time of the guest, the time of the group, and the time of the studio appointment. Our group went through issues with guests getting sick, group members having trouble getting there, and so on. Thankfully, I think I managed to communicate clearly with the guest, make bold decisions to move things forward, and ensure that the group was able to work together happily and efficiently by planning the timing and content of everyone&#8217;s responsibilities.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">But I wasn&#8217;t very happy with the content of the podcast. I planned the podcast in the direction of a light talk show and wrote the outline for the podcast. As a result the show was a little less professional and serious. If I could redo it, I would consider adding more in-depth discussion topics.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">Also, I don&#8217;t think I was proficient enough at hosting the podcast and the group members who conducted the recording were not relaxed enough. During the recording, there were quite a few slips of the tongue by myself and other groupmates which I had to edit out. This resulted in a lot of unnatural cuts in the show, which greatly affected the viewing experience. This could have been avoided if we had been able to work on our verbal and mental skills more.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/30/report-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Design By Accident &#8211; 主题海报设计</title>
		<link>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/07/design-by-accident-%e4%b8%bb%e9%a2%98%e6%b5%b7%e6%8a%a5%e8%ae%be%e8%ae%a1/</link>
					<comments>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/07/design-by-accident-%e4%b8%bb%e9%a2%98%e6%b5%b7%e6%8a%a5%e8%ae%be%e8%ae%a1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[W]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 02:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[平面设计]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/?p=118</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[基于展览《Design By Accident》主题完成的课程作业，我简单展示了思路和过程。]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="2000" height="1125" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/PMD-Poster-Weng-Yiyang1_page-0002.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-119"/></figure>



<p>基于展览《Design By Accident》主题完成的课程作业，我简单展示了思路和过程。</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="2000" height="1125" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/PMD-Poster-Weng-Yiyang1_page-0003.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-120"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="2000" height="1125" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/PMD-Poster-Weng-Yiyang1_page-0004.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-121"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="2000" height="1125" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/PMD-Poster-Weng-Yiyang1_page-0005.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-122"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="2000" height="1125" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/PMD-Poster-Weng-Yiyang1_page-0006.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-123"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="2000" height="1125" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/PMD-Poster-Weng-Yiyang1_page-0007.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-124"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="2000" height="1125" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/PMD-Poster-Weng-Yiyang1_page-0008.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-125"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="2000" height="1125" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/PMD-Poster-Weng-Yiyang1_page-0009.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-126"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="2000" height="1125" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/PMD-Poster-Weng-Yiyang1_page-0010.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-127"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="2000" height="1125" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/PMD-Poster-Weng-Yiyang1_page-0011.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-128"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="2000" height="1125" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/PMD-Poster-Weng-Yiyang1_page-0012.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-129"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="2000" height="1125" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/PMD-Poster-Weng-Yiyang1_page-0013.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-130"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="2000" height="1125" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/PMD-Poster-Weng-Yiyang1_page-0014.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-131"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="2000" height="1125" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/PMD-Poster-Weng-Yiyang1_page-0015.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-132"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="2000" height="1125" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/PMD-Poster-Weng-Yiyang1_page-0016.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-133"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="2000" height="1125" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/PMD-Poster-Weng-Yiyang1_page-0017.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-134"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="2000" height="1125" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/PMD-Poster-Weng-Yiyang1_page-0018.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-135"/></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/07/design-by-accident-%e4%b8%bb%e9%a2%98%e6%b5%b7%e6%8a%a5%e8%ae%be%e8%ae%a1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>黄蝴蝶飞舞之日</title>
		<link>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/07/%e9%bb%84%e8%9d%b4%e8%9d%b6%e9%a3%9e%e8%88%9e%e4%b9%8b%e6%97%a5/</link>
					<comments>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/07/%e9%bb%84%e8%9d%b4%e8%9d%b6%e9%a3%9e%e8%88%9e%e4%b9%8b%e6%97%a5/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[W]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 01:57:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[企划]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/?p=103</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[原创幻想故事《黄蝴蝶飞舞之日》的相关设计]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="3508" height="4961" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/封面.png" alt="" class="wp-image-105"/></figure>



<p>《黄蝴蝶飞舞之日》是我基于现实中墨西哥传统节日亡灵节创作的幻想故事。现已作为COC风格的TRPG游戏模组在平台[魔都]和[骰声回响]发布。</p>



<p>这里展示了我对这部作品电影海报化和相关周边产品设计的设想。</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1275" height="1650" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Final-assignment_page-0002.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-106"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1275" height="1650" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Final-assignment_page-0003.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-107"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1275" height="1650" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Final-assignment_page-0004.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-108"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1275" height="1650" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Final-assignment_page-0005.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-109"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1275" height="1650" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Final-assignment_page-0006.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-110"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1275" height="1650" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Final-assignment_page-0007.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-111"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1275" height="1650" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Final-assignment_page-0008.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-112"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1275" height="1650" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Final-assignment_page-0009.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-113"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1275" height="1650" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Final-assignment_page-0010.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-114"/></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/07/%e9%bb%84%e8%9d%b4%e8%9d%b6%e9%a3%9e%e8%88%9e%e4%b9%8b%e6%97%a5/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>镜子和影子</title>
		<link>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/07/%e9%95%9c%e5%ad%90%e5%92%8c%e5%bd%b1%e5%ad%90/</link>
					<comments>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/07/%e9%95%9c%e5%ad%90%e5%92%8c%e5%bd%b1%e5%ad%90/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[W]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 01:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Q版绘画]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/?p=85</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[为喜欢的竞技体育选手绘制的fanart，写了绘画过程的笔记]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1080" height="1080" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/2024040605.png" alt="" class="wp-image-86"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1000" height="1000" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/20240406001.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-87"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1000" height="1000" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/20240406002.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-88"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1000" height="1000" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/20240406003.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-89"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1000" height="1000" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/20240406004.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-91"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1000" height="1000" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/20240406005-1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-92"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1000" height="1000" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/20240406006.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-93"/></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/07/%e9%95%9c%e5%ad%90%e5%92%8c%e5%bd%b1%e5%ad%90/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>魔王和勇者</title>
		<link>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/07/%e9%ad%94%e7%8e%8b%e5%92%8c%e5%8b%87%e8%80%85/</link>
					<comments>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/07/%e9%ad%94%e7%8e%8b%e5%92%8c%e5%8b%87%e8%80%85/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[W]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 01:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Q版绘画]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/?p=81</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[自己设计的西方幻想童话设定插图，录制并剪辑发布了绘画过程]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1000" height="1000" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/20240226.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-82"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-video"><video controls src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/3月14日_x264.mp4"></video></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/07/%e9%ad%94%e7%8e%8b%e5%92%8c%e5%8b%87%e8%80%85/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		<enclosure url="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/3月14日_x264.mp4" length="13696475" type="video/mp4" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>月球时代白日梦</title>
		<link>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/07/%e6%9c%88%e7%90%83%e6%97%b6%e4%bb%a3%e7%99%bd%e6%97%a5%e6%a2%a6/</link>
					<comments>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/07/%e6%9c%88%e7%90%83%e6%97%b6%e4%bb%a3%e7%99%bd%e6%97%a5%e6%a2%a6/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[W]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Q版绘画]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/?p=78</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[为朋友的小说《月球时代白日梦》绘制的插图]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center is-style-default is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>&#8220;This is Ground Control to Major Tom,You&#8217;ve really made the grade, And the papers want to know who shirts you wear…&#8221;</p>
<cite>铅笔慢慢地从吉米的手里飘起来，在空中打了个转，碰到了舷窗的玻璃之上，似乎唯恐将这坚固的玻璃撞碎，它又打了个转，飞到了亚历克斯的手套旁边，亚历克斯握住了这个摆脱了地球引力的小家伙，将它别在了吉米上衣的口袋里。<br>年轻的吉米向前来送行的人群告别，彩带伴随着纯色的花瓣落在干燥的地面，浅浅的浮尘在他的身边飞舞，搞得他鼻子痒痒的，法属圭亚那今天天气晴朗，天空湛蓝。发射台上的大家伙熠熠生辉，白色的涂料舒适且亮眼，工人们在进行着最后的检修，她看起来像只漂亮的白鸟。几位优秀的航天员们即将离开这个迷人的地方，开启一段遥远且漫长的旅途，可能永不归来。<br>吉米看着母亲的眼睛，他知道她在无声的告别，母亲将花朵别在吉米手套旁，手套旁有一个小镜子，反射着太阳的光线，母亲别过头去，似乎不想让她的孩子看见泪水，吉米觉得有些声音在里他远去，泪水在倒流，往天上飞。<br>他想起小时候看见父亲的剪报上，加加林飞向太空的旧闻，父亲让他有些生气，因为父亲居然把加加林去世的消息和这个贴在一起，他知道这个俄国人去了太空，他是第一个，他知道他死于地球而非太空。多酷的家伙啊。吉米的脑子里幻想着，某日能飞向那个遥远的地方，远离伦敦的臭水沟，自己一个人静静地待上108分钟。父亲说，当然也可以做得到，因为这个俄国佬也是工人的儿子。<br>亚历克斯拍了拍吉米的肩，该走了。<br>他擦了擦吉米的泪，他一直都想着去更远的地方，他享受着失重的感觉，那是世界上任何一种药品都难以企及的快感。亚历克斯仍然记得加加林来到英国的场景，伦敦的街头到处都热闹非凡，多么神奇的家伙啊，他的笑容居然能融化冷战的壁垒！这家伙没有他想象中的那样高大，似乎比亚历克斯矮一些，但这个俄国佬可去过更高的地方，所有的人都在欢呼，似乎已经能看见女王窗台上招手了，亚历克斯跟着车队，看着他们驶向海格特墓园，去给那个德国人献花。</cite></blockquote>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1000" height="1000" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/20240410001.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-79"/></figure>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p></p>
</blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/07/%e6%9c%88%e7%90%83%e6%97%b6%e4%bb%a3%e7%99%bd%e6%97%a5%e6%a2%a6/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>速写合集</title>
		<link>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/06/%e9%80%9f%e5%86%99%e5%90%88%e9%9b%86/</link>
					<comments>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/06/%e9%80%9f%e5%86%99%e5%90%88%e9%9b%86/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[W]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 01:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[正比绘画]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/?p=61</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[一组21年到22年的速写，以竞技体育为主题，均有参考照片]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="3035" height="2150" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/0.9.png" alt="" class="wp-image-62"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="3035" height="2150" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/0.14.png" alt="" class="wp-image-63"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="3035" height="2150" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/0.19.png" alt="" class="wp-image-64"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="3035" height="2150" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/0.37.png" alt="" class="wp-image-65"/></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/06/%e9%80%9f%e5%86%99%e5%90%88%e9%9b%86/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>三叶草和皇冠</title>
		<link>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/06/%e4%b8%89%e5%8f%b6%e8%8d%89%e5%92%8c%e7%9a%87%e5%86%a0/</link>
					<comments>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/06/%e4%b8%89%e5%8f%b6%e8%8d%89%e5%92%8c%e7%9a%87%e5%86%a0/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[W]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Q版绘画]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/?p=50</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[以三叶草和皇冠为主题的绘画，献给朋友的作品，附带了绘画过程展示]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1000" height="1000" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/2024030502.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-51"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1000" height="1000" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/2024030504.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-52"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1000" height="1000" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/2024030505.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-53"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1000" height="1000" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/2024030506.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-54"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1000" height="1000" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/2024030507.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-55"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1000" height="1000" src="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/2024030508.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-56"/></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/06/%e4%b8%89%e5%8f%b6%e8%8d%89%e5%92%8c%e7%9a%87%e5%86%a0/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
