<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Report &#8211; Yuanzi</title>
	<atom:link href="https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/category/report/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi</link>
	<description>See the world with different perspectives</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 06:30:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>zh-CN</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Report 2-4</title>
		<link>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/31/report-2-4/</link>
					<comments>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/31/report-2-4/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[W]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 02:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Report]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/?p=190</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Group-6 I was very impressed with Group-6&#8217;s podcast, t&#8230;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Group-6</strong></h2>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">I was very impressed with Group-6&#8217;s podcast, the guests, the content of the dialogue and the post-production were all very professional.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">The topic of this podcast is how to build a personal brand on social media. Firstly, know yourself and find out what makes you unique. For me, this is a very important piece of advice. I had a dream of becoming a freelance artist, but I wasn&#8217;t sure what made me unique as a person. What I&#8217;m good at, what I like and what the public likes, I&#8217;ve been trying to find where these three areas intersect. Maybe I also have to understand and work out in which area I can make my personal identity.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">Also, my guest mentioned updating her social media accounts for a long time, which is something I often forget. I&#8217;m not good at sticking to things, I often try different directions, create different accounts, and abandon and forget my social media accounts because I get busy. If I am determined to run my own social media, I should stick with it as a business.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">Later on, both the guest and the Group6 interview touched on the period of time to start running a personal brand and discussed whether you should start as early as possible or wait until the time is right to start. I&#8217;ve rarely thought about this aspect of my life, and I probably haven&#8217;t been serious enough about running a social media business before. I&#8217;m actually graduating soon and have to start thinking about employment, and personal branding is crucial if I&#8217;m going to be a freelance artist. I have to start thinking deeply and planning how my social media will be run.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Group-5</h2>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">Group-5&#8217;s podcast explores the life of Gen Z influencers.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">I rarely look at Instagram and TikTok and lack knowledge about influencers on both platforms. The life of influencers as depicted in the podcast has greatly expanded my horizons.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">The guest&#8217;s internet persona may be more typical of Singaporean social media platforms, but this type of internet persona is rare on Chinese social media platforms.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">In China, there is not a huge market for very young, asset-hungry, luxury-loving female netizens. Young fashion bloggers usually portray the image of students who use affordable fashion and beauty products. It is only fashion bloggers over twenty-five years old who start discussing luxury goods. In China, the number of young students who can consume luxury goods is small, and few fashion bloggers target this market.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">Society very much discourages young people from high spending, which has to do with the economy, culture and so on. The government does not support young people investing their money in luxuries. East Asian parents are against young people having too much disposable money. Young luxury consumers are not big enough to get a voice in the mainstream media. People who have difficulty consuming luxury goods loathe the image of rich young people. I was struck by the differences in the internet ecosystem presented by this comparison. I started to think that when running social media accounts in different regions, it might be important to have a deep understanding of different social cultures and online ecology. The Internet society is equally society, and perhaps sociological knowledge can help us to have a deeper understanding of the media.<br></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Group-2</h2>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">I really enjoyed this episode of the podcast, meticulously delivered with a lot of useful content. E-commerce is a very promising industry and is closely related to media. In the future, it is foreseeable that the e-commerce sector will demand more and more media professionals. This is a career path to consider.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">The ability to learn will be a basic quality requirement for this industry. The guest mentioned that he and many of his team members did not come from media background, but the guest showed an in-depth understanding of the media field, and you can see that the guest has knowledge of supply chain and other different aspects. E-commerce is a very competitive field in China, and it&#8217;s clear that having media-related knowledge and diploma is not enough.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">The guest shared a lot of personal experience about what it takes to work in the media. I think it can be summarised in one word: ‘Understanding’.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">Understanding of the self, the self is the practitioner himself, or the brand itself. Firstly, media practitioners need to have a clear understanding of their own abilities and passions. Only by knowing what they want to do and what they are capable of doing can they avoid the two great tests of ‘commercialisation’ and ‘high work pressure’ as the guest said. Brands also need to have a clear understanding of themselves, and I think the guest&#8217;s analogy of social media being the face of the brand is a good one. Consumers are no longer paying for illusory brands, and there is a general trend for consumers to be more receptive to brands that ‘feel like a person’. I&#8217;ve seen a lot of brands that are very vague about ‘who I really am’ and ‘what I really look like’, so how can a brand without a face gain the trust of consumers?</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">Understanding of others, the others are collaborators and consumers. Only by understanding the needs of the partners, such as the example of the little girl mentioned by the guest, can we achieve a win-win situation. Only by understanding the competencies of the partner, such as the blogger who is good at presenting scientific knowledge, as mentioned by the guest, can we maximise the effect of the collaboration. The understanding of the consumer is even more important. Firstly, who are you selling to? Second, what do they want? </p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">Media is an industry that serves people, and when you express yourself, you have to be heard, and they can understand and accept it for your expression to be meaningful. This is often not a question of ability but a question of mindset, you need to draw closer to the consumer, deep into their hearts, and even understand and feel what they themselves may not be able to understand and feel.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/31/report-2-4/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report 1</title>
		<link>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/30/report-1/</link>
					<comments>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/30/report-1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[W]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 06:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Report]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/?p=165</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The main takeaway that this assignment gave me was that I ac&#8230;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">The main takeaway that this assignment gave me was that I actually experienced how to communicate and collaborate with professionals or group members.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">After understanding the assignment, I first discussed the list of possible guests to invite with my group. I know a little about freelance painters in China, so I first considered inviting from this field. After contacting several artists, I received some positive responses. In the end, I chose an artist who had experience as a professional cartoonist and was now freelancing and running her own personal media account. Our group thought her career history would be valuable to discuss, so we planned an entire podcast on the topic.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">This guest studied accounting in college, then went on to work in the comics industry before finally choosing to freelance. So I divided the podcast into three parts, the first being how to switch from an unrelated major to drawing comics, the second being the experience of working in comics, and the third being running a personal account. I think these are the areas that will be of interest to the students, and the guest will be able to offer her own experiences.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">I was responsible for planning the podcast, communicating with the guests, hosting the podcast and a little editing. Communicating with the guest put a lot of pressure on me because she had a lot of work experience, was well-known on the Chinese internet, and was much older than me. Negotiating the details of the podcast, scheduling the recording and so on was very stressful. Scheduling takes into account the time of the guest, the time of the group, and the time of the studio appointment. Our group went through issues with guests getting sick, group members having trouble getting there, and so on. Thankfully, I think I managed to communicate clearly with the guest, make bold decisions to move things forward, and ensure that the group was able to work together happily and efficiently by planning the timing and content of everyone&#8217;s responsibilities.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">But I wasn&#8217;t very happy with the content of the podcast. I planned the podcast in the direction of a light talk show and wrote the outline for the podcast. As a result the show was a little less professional and serious. If I could redo it, I would consider adding more in-depth discussion topics.</p>



<p class="has-base-font-size" style="line-height:1.7">Also, I don&#8217;t think I was proficient enough at hosting the podcast and the group members who conducted the recording were not relaxed enough. During the recording, there were quite a few slips of the tongue by myself and other groupmates which I had to edit out. This resulted in a lot of unnatural cuts in the show, which greatly affected the viewing experience. This could have been avoided if we had been able to work on our verbal and mental skills more.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://weng0147.github.io/Yuanzi/2024/05/30/report-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
